Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- College Files, Series IV
  - Indonesia
    - Satya Wacana Christian University
      - Buildings: Jensen House, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 1580)
      - Buildings: Smith House, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 1581)
      - Consultation, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 1582)
      - Dutch Working Group - correspondence [see also: Working Group - Amsterdam], 1977-1978 (Box 111, Folder 1583)
      - Dwidjantara, Silas, 1972-1978 (Box 111, Folder 1584)
      - East Asia Student Encounter Program (E.A.S.E.), 1979 (Box 111, Folder 1585)
      - English Department, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 1586)
      - Faculty Development Fellowship, 1973-1975 (Box 111, Folder 1587)
      - Faculty - Overseas Personnel, 1969-1976 (Box 111, Folder 1588)
      - Finance - Budgets Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 111, Folder 1589-1590)
      - Finance - Donors in U.S., 1975 (Box 112, Folder 1592)
      - Goeltenboth, F., 1976-1979 (Box 112, Folder 1593)
      - Gosita, Afife, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 1594)
      - Guidance and Counseling Center, 1971-1978 (Box 112, Folder 1595-1596)
      - Gultom, Richard, 1972-1974 (Box 112, Folder 1597)
      - Hamakonda, Ertien S., 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 1598)
      - Hamakonda, Towa P., 1972 (Box 112, Folder 1599)
      - Hope, Angela E. [see also: Guidance Counselling Center and Scholarships], 1971-1978 (Box 112, Folder 1600-1601)
      - Indonesian Language, 1973-1975 (Box 112, Folder 1602)
      - Jenson, Kenneth and Norma, 1971-1979 (Box 112, Folder 1603)
      - Kana, Nico [see also: Research Institute in Social Sciences], 1973-1977 (Box 112, Folder 1604)
      - Kastow, Hadi, 1973
      - King, Annie, 1977
      - King, Douglas, 1971-1978 (Box 112, Folder 1605)
      - Laboratory Project, 1971-1978 (Box 112, Folder 1606, Box 113, Folder 1607)
      - Library, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 1608)
      - Ngandji, K., 1972
      - Netherlands Group, 1973-1979
      - Notohamidjojo, O., 1971-1976 (Box 113, Folder 1609)
      - Overall Development Commission, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 1610)
      - Overseas Personnel, 1975-1979 (Box 113, Folder 1611)
      - Pentico, George, 1964-1979 (Box 113, Folder 1612-1613)
      - Pradono, Wahjo, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 1614)
      - Press "Tirta Amerta", 1972
      - Pre-University Course, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 1615)
      - Printing Press, 1972-1975
      - Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 113, Folder 1616)
      - Publications, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 1617)
      - Purwanto, Darmo, 1974
      - Rahardjamulja, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 1618)
      - Rector [see: Sutarno (Rector)]
      - Reports, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 1619)
      - Research Institute in Social Sciences [see also: Kana, Nico L.], 1967 (Box 113, Folder 1620)
      - Satya Wacana Press, 1977-1978 (Box 114, Folder 1621)
      - Siliwole Djoeroemana, 1971-1975 (Box 114, Folder 1622)
      - Siswohardjono, Arjatmi [see also: Guidance Counselling Center], 1969-1977 (Box 114, Folder 1623)
      - S - General (Box 114, Folder 1624)
      - Statistics, 1972
      - Sutarno (Rector), 1972-1979 (Box 114, Folder 1625)
      - Tanutama, T. A. [see also: Satya Wacana Press], 1971-1974 (Box 114, Folder 1626)
      - Tjahjakartana, Hermawan, 1973-1976 (Box 114, Folder 1627)
      - Tjahjakartana, Othniel, 1971-1974 (Box 114, Folder 1628)
      - Toisuta, Willi, 1976-1979 (Box 114, Folder 1629)
      - Translation Project, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 1630)
      - Van Emmerik, Fred, 1970-1974 (Box 114, Folder 1631)
      - Water Supply Project, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 1632)
      - Wilardjo, Liek, 1973-1978 (Box 114, Folder 1633)
      - Wasis, Sastroredjo, 1976-1979 (Box 114, Folder 1634)
      - Working Group - Amsterdam [see also: Dutch Working Group], 1972-1975 (Box 114, Folder 1635)
  - Japan
    - Japan International Christian University
      - A - D General (Box 115, Folder 1636)
      - Admissions Program Dispute, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 1637)
      - Asian Religion / Korean Studies (Chairs), 1977 (Box 115, Folder 1638)
      - Cho, Kiyoko, 1965-1977 (Box 115, Folder 1639)
      - Classes, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 1640)
      - Faculty - Overseas Personnel, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 1641)
      - Finance, 1973-1977 (Box 115, Folder 1642)
      - Gazette, 1973-1974 (Box 115, Folder 1643)
      - General Correspondence, 1963-1978 (Box 115, Folder 1644-1645)
      - Histake, Masao (President), 1967-1969 (Box 115, Folder 1646)
      - I - L General (Box 115, Folder 1647)
      - I.C.U.-U.B.C.H.E.A. Scholarship, 1981-1982 (Box 115, Folder 1648)
      - Information Questionnaire, 1972-1977 (Box 115, Folder 1649)
      - Institute of Asian Cultural Studies [see also: Cho, Kiyoko], 1971-1977 (Box 115, Folder 1650)
      - International Educational Exchange [see: Tsuru, Harou]
      - Japan International Christian University Foundation - Joint UBCHEA Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 116, Folder 1651)
      - Katayama, Wataru (Librarian), 1972 (Box 116, Folder 1652)
      - Kim, Young-jak, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 1653)
      - Library [see: Katayama, Wataru (Librarian)]
      - Miyake, Akira, 1969-1973 (Box 116, Folder 1654)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu, 1975-1983 (Box 116, Folder 1655)
      - Overseas Personnel, 1977-1980 (Box 116, Folder 1656)
      - Professor Exchange, 1962-1963 (Box 116, Folder 1657)
      - Project Evaluation, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 1658)
      - Project Proposals, 1975-1983 (Box 116, Folder 1659-1660)
      - Purchasing, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 1661)
      - Q - T General (Box 116, Folder 1662)
      - Scholarships (UBCHEA), 1955-1971 (Box 116, Folder 1663-1664)
      - Scholarships (UBCHEA), 1971-1978 (Box 117, Folder 1665)
      - Science Hall, 1968 (Box 117, Folder 1666)
      - Shorrock, Hallam, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 1667)
      - Sinoto, Yosito, 1971-1975 (Box 117, Folder 1668)
      - Tabuci, Minora (Vice-President) [see: Finance]
      - Tam, Kwok-chi [see: ICU-UBCHEA Scholarship]
      - Tour of East Asia (U.B.), 1969 Fall (Box 117, Folder 1669)
      - Troyer, Maurice E. (Values Study), 1963-1966 (Box 117, Folder 1670-1672)
      - Tsuru, Harou (International Educational Exchange), 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 1673)
      - Ukai, Nobushige, 1963-1966 (Box 117, Folder 1674)
      - Values Study [see: Troyer, Maurice W.]
      - Visiting Professors, 1972-1974 (Box 117, Folder 1675)
      - Worth, Donald, 1973-1979 (Box 117, Folder 1676)
      - Year Abroad Program, 1967-1974 (Box 117, Folder 1677)
      - Yuasa, Hachiro, 1979, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 1678)
      - Yung, Ying Yu, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 1679)
    - Sophia University
      - Pittau, S.J., Rev. Joseph (President), 1977-1979 (Box 117, Folder 1680)
  - Korea
    - Ewha Woman's University
      - Chung, Ii Sook (President), 1979 (Box 117, Folder 1681)
      - Information Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1682)
      - Kim, Okgill (President), 1964-1979 (Box 118, Folder 1683)
      - Korean Christian Faculty Fellowship, 1973-1979 (Box 118, Folder 1684)
      - Korean Women's Institute, 1977-1979 (Box 118, Folder 1685)
      - Library Survey, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 1686)
      - Overseas Personnel List, 1977-1979 (Box 118, Folder 1687)
      - Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1977-1980 (Box 118, Folder 1688)
      - Science Curriculum Project (Suh, David K.), 1977-1979 (Box 118, Folder 1689)
    - Keimyung University
      - Computer, 1972-1975 (Box 118, Folder 1690)
      - Information Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1691)
      - Overseas Personnel List, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 1692)
      - Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1976-1980 (Box 118, Folder 1693)
      - Synn, Ilhi, 1978-1979 (Box 118, Folder 1694)
      - Synn, Taisik, 1972-1978 (Box 118, Folder 1695)
      - Background / Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 118, Folder 1696)
      - Central Library, 1978-1981 (Box 118, Folder 1697, Box 119, Folder 1698)
      - Correspondence (General), 1976 (Box 119, Folder 1699)
      - Koh, Bum Soe, 1976-1979 (Box 119, Folder 1700)
      - Lee, Hahn Been, 1971-1977 (Box 119, Folder 1701)
      - Overseas Personnel List, 1975-1979 (Box 119, Folder 1702)
      - Prince, C. E., 1975-1979 (Box 119, Folder 1703)
      - Proposals, Grants, Closing Reports, 1973/74-1978/79 (Box 119, Folder 1704-1706)
      - Proposals, Grants, Closing Reports, 1978/79-1979/80 (Box 120, Folder 1707-1708)
    - Yonsei University
      - Agricultural Development, Institute of, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 1709)
      - Ahn, Se Hee, 1976-1979 (Box 120, Folder 1710)
      - Background, Information, Reports, etc., 1971-1979 (Box 120, Folder 1711)
      - Campus Plans, 1970 (Box 120, Folder 1712)
      - Certificate of Donation Statements, 1976, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 1713-1715)
      - Choi, Hochin, 1976-1978 (Box 120, Folder 1716)
      - Constitution and By-laws, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 1717)
      - Education Research, Institute of, 1976-1978 (Box 121, Folder 1718)
      - Environmental Pollution Research, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 1719)
      - Finance: Budget Correspondence (Underwood), 1976-1979 (Box 121, Folder 1720-1723)
      - History of University, 1964-1969 (Box 121, Folder 1724)
      - Hoon, Hyun Sang, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 1725)
      - Ki, Hyoung Oh [see: Education Research, Institute of], 1979
      - Kim, Dae Joon, 1977
      - Kim, Donguk
      - Kim, Young Hoon [see: University Planning and Development]
      - Kim, Youtaik, Estate of, 1976-1977 (Box 121, Folder 1726)
      - Kwon, Sook Pyo [see: Environmental Pollution Research]
      - Lee, A-Z, 1978-1979 (Box 121, Folder 1727)
      - Lee, Woo Choo, 1976-1979 (Box 121, Folder 1728)
      - Lew, Joon, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 1729)
      - Library, General, 1976-1980
      - Maw, Thelma, 1979 (Box 121, Folder 1730)
      - Noh, Jong Sun, 1976
      - Organization, Administration, 1958-1962
      - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1977-1979 (Box 121, Folder 1731)
      - Park, Young Ki, 1975-1977 (Box 121, Folder 1732)
      - Park, Young Sik, 1969-1973 (Box 121, Folder 1733)
      - Park, Young Sik, 1973-1975 (Box 122, Folder 1734)
      - Peace Corps Project, 1967-1970 (Box 122, Folder 1735)
      - Proposals, Grants, Project Reports, End Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 122, Folder 1736-1740)
      - Ro, Chung-hyun [see: Urban Studies and Development, Institute of]
      - Rural Community Health Teaching Project, 1975-1979 (Box 122, Folder 1741)
      - Rural Community Health Teaching Project: Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 123, Folder 1742)
      - Purchasing and Shipments - Correspondence, General, 1977-1979 (Box 123, Folder 1743-1744)
      - Purchasing and Shipments - Correspondence, re. Orders, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 1745)
      - Purchasing and Shipments - Requisitions, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1746)
      - Purchasing and Shipments -Reports: 251 Clearing Accounts, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 1747)
      - Purchasing and Shipments - Library Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 124, Folder 1748)
      - Questionnaire (Information), 1977 (Box 124, Folder 1749)
      - "Recommendations on the Function of the U.B.C.H.E.A. from Yonsei University", 1971 (Box 124, Folder 1750)
      - Research Grants, 1965-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1751-1752)
      - Rhee, Byung Mock, 1972-1974 (Box 124, Folder 1753)
      - Rice, Roberta, 1975 (Box 124, Folder 1754)
      - Robb, Ian S., 1978
      - Royce, Edith M. Scholarship Fund, 1968-1977 (Box 124, Folder 1755)
      - Scholarships, 1977-1979 (Box 124, Folder 1756)
      - Seal, Motto, Colors, Etc., n.d. (Box 124, Folder 1757)
      - Sol, Song-Kyong, 1973
      - Student Union Counseling Center, 1977
      - Symposium "Innovation in Christian Higher Education", 1972 (Box 124, Folder 1758)
      - Tieszen, Helen Rose, 1973, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 1759)
      - Underwood, Horace G., 1971-1979 (Box 124, Folder 1760-1763)
      - Univac Computer, 1969-1972 (Box 125, Folder 1764)
      - University Planning Development, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 1765)
      - Urban Studies Development, Institute of, 1969-1979 (Box 125, Folder 1765-1766)
      - Weiss, Ernest W.
      - Personal, 1971-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1767)
      - Shipments, College of Medicine, 1972-1973 (Box 125, Folder 1768)
      - Y - General (Box 125, Folder 1769)
      - Yoon, Byung Sang, 1973-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1770)
      - Yoon, Ki Jung, 1972-1973 (Box 125, Folder 1771)
    - Yonsei Medical Center
      - Administrative Council - Minutes (Box 126, Folder 1776)
      - Buildings, 1972-1974 (Box 126, Folder 1776)
      - Chang, Woon Sup, 1976
      - "China Medical Board Endowment Fund for Yonsei University College of Medicine", 1976-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1777)
      - Class of 1960 Fund [see: Medicine, College of]
      - Curriculum - Community Medicine, 1975-1976 (Box 126, Folder 1778)
      - Cho, Jung Sil, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 1779)
      - Dental College, 1973-1974
      - Eiloart, Gail, 1975
      - K - General (Box 126, Folder 1780)
      - Kim, Dong Sik, 1966-1973
      - Kim, Hyo Kyu, 1975-1979
      - Medical Complex - Master Plan, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 1781)
      - Medicine, College of - Class of 1960 Fund, 1975-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1782)
      - Miranda, Jaime, 1973-1975 (Box 126, Folder 1783)
      - Missionary Personnel, 1975-1976 (Box 126, Folder 1784)
      - Missionary Personnel, Nursing, College of
      - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1785)
      - Five Year Development Plan, 1974-1980 (Box 126, Folder 1786)
      - Scholarships, 1974-1975 (Box 126, Folder 1787)
      - Orthopedic Traveling Fellowship Fund, 1973-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1788)
      - Outreach Materials/Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1789)
      - Pain Clinic, 1972-1973 (Box 126, Folder 1790)
      - Presbyterian Medical Center, 1977
      - Rehabilitation Medicine, Institute of, 1977-1979 (Box 126, Folder 1791)
      - Shin, Jung Soon [see: Rehabilitation Medicine, Institute of]
      - Sich, Dorothea, 1973-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1792)
      - Wonju Christian Hospital, 1976-1979 (Box 127, Folder 1793)
      - Yang, Jae Mo, 1973-1976 (Box 127, Folder 1794)
      - Yonhee Community Health Service, 1972-1974 (Box 127, Folder 1795)
  - Philippines
    - Central Philippine University
      - Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 127, Folder 1796-1798)
    - De La Salle University
      - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1799-1800)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 128, Folder 1801)
      - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1977-1978 (Box 128, Folder 1802)
      - Proposals, Grants, Correspondence, 1973-1974, 1979-1980 (Box 128, Folder 1803)
    - Northern Christian College
      - Lagon, Filemon L., 1977-1979 (Box 128, Folder 1804)
      - N.C.C. in the Philippines - MASCOM Network, 1971-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1805)
      - Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1977-1979 (Box 128, Folder 1806)
      - Reports, Manuals, Etc., 1978-1979
    - Philippine Christian College [became Philippine Christian University in 1976]
      - Arquiza, Lino Q., 1971-1976 (Box 128, Folder 1807)
      - Borlazo, Gregorio, 1969-1976 (Box 128, Folder 1808)
      - Fellowships, 1968-1975 (Box 128, Folder 1809)
      - Flood Relief, 1971
      - Finance - Budget Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 128, Folder 1810)
      - Finance - Library (invoices), 1973 (Box 128, Folder 1811)
      - Go, Jesus, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 1812)
      - Nursing (Mary Johnston College of Nursing), 1971-1979
      - Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 128, Folder 1813)
      - Puno, Carlito, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 1814)
      - Puno, Leven S., 1973-1974
      - Research and Development - Science, 1971-1975 (Box 129, Folder 1815)
      - Science Department, 1971-1973 (Box 129, Folder 1816)
      - Statistics, 1971-1973
      - Tovera, David G., 1970-1975 (Box 129, Folder 1817-1818)
    - Philippine Christian University
      - Arquiza, Lino Q., 1976-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1819)
      - Background, 1971-1978 (Box 129, Folder 1820)
      - Book Orders, 1976
      - Gomes, Hilario M., 1978 (Box 129, Folder 1821)
      - Merger (Philippine Christian Univ. Union Theological Seminary), 1977-1978
      - Ocampo, Patrocinio S., 1979 (Box 129, Folder 1822)
      - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1975-1976
      - Philippine Christian Educational Foundation, Inc., 1971 (Box 129, Folder 1823)
      - President's Report, 1976-1977 (Box 129, Folder 1824)
      - Project Proposals, 1974-1980 (Box 129, Folder 1825)
      - Resurreccion, Gloria Q., 1979 (Box 129, Folder 1826)
      - Ting, Simon, 1976-1977
    - Silliman University
      - Alcala, Angel C., 1976-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1827)
      - Alegado, Gideon Z. Rachel, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 1828)
      - Apilado, Mariano C., 1976-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1829)
      - Apura, Patrocinio Anir, 1976-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1830)
      - Bandoquillo, Venancio S., 1979 (Box 130, Folder 1831)
      - Batchelor, Charles (Fund), 1976-1979
      - Biology (Teaching Seminar), 1976
      - Bookstore, 1976-1977 (Box 130, Folder 1832)
      - By-laws and Articles of Incorporation, 1971
      - Ceniza, Riorita, 1976-1978 (Box 130, Folder 1833)
      - Corsino, MacArthur F., 1971-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1834)
      - Cultural Center Research Projects [see: Reynolds, Hubert]
      - Divinity School, 1976-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1835)
      - Dormal, Quintin S. [see also: Finance - Budget Correspondence], 1976-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1836-1837)
      - Elwood, Douglas and Bettie, 1976-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1838)
      - Endowment Fund, 1968-1976 (Box 130, Folder 1839)
      - Extension Program [see also: Lecciones, Eduardo C.], 1976-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1840-1841)
      - Faculty-Staff Development Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 131, Folder 1842)
      - Faurot, Albert, 1976-1979 (Box 131, Folder 1843)
      - Finance - Budget Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 131, Folder 1844-1847)
      - Fontelo, C. [see: Finance - Budget Correspondence]
      - H - General, 1978 (Box 131, Folder 1848)
      - Honors Program, 1976-1977
      - Ilano, Josefa M., 1971-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1849)
      - Information Questionnaire, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 1850)
      - Instructional Development Center [see: Tayko, Perla]
      - Integrated Community Development Program, n.d. (Box 131, Folder 1851)
      - Jacobs, Abby R. [NOTE: The monographs We Did Not Surrender and Leaves from a War Diary have been removed from this file. They are now located in Pamphlet Series "A". Please consult ORBIS.]
      - Keiling, Hanns Peter, 1976-1977 (Box 131, Folder 1852)
      - Kapili, Pascual, 1977
      - Lacar, Luis Q., 1976-1979 (Box 131, Folder 1853)
      - Law, Dale R., 1976-1979 (Box 131, Folder 1854)
      - Lecciones, Eduardo C., 1976 (Box 131, Folder 1855)
      - Leonardia, Amiel Y., 1977-1979 (Box 132, Folder 1856)
      - Library, 1976-1978 (Box 132, Folder 1857)
      - Malayang, Sammy, 1979-1980 (Box 132, Folder 1858)
      - Marine Laboratory Project
      - Martinez, Salvador T., 1976-1979 (Box 132, Folder 1859)
      - Maslog, Crispin, 1977-1979
      - Medical Center - Workshops and Projects, 1976-1978 (Box 132, Folder 1860)
      - Montebon, Jose Jr., 1976
      - Negrito, Mt. Development Project, 1976-1978 (Box 132, Folder 1861)
      - Nursing, College of [see also: Roble, Maria Conception], 1976-1977
      - Nutrition Program, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 1862)
      - Ongcog, N. [see: Finance - Budget Correspondence and Purchasing Shipments]
      - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1976-1979 (Box 132, Folder 1862)
      - Pak, Harry Y., 1976 (Box 132, Folder 1863)
      - Palmore, James A., 1976-1978
      - Purchasing
      - Medical Center, 1976-1979 (Box 132, Folder 1864)
      - Personal Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 132, Folder 1865)
      - Pfeiffer, Ruth Imperial, 1975-1979 (Box 132, Folder 1866)
      - Project Evaluations, 1978-1980 (Box 132, Folder 1867)
      - Proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 1868)
      - Proposals, 1977-1980 (Box 133, Folder 1869-1870)
      - Extension Program, 1977-1978 (Box 133, Folder 1871)
      - Printed Matter/Publications, c. 1973 (Box 133, Folder 1872)
      - Purchasing and Shipments: Invoices, 1976-1979 (Box 133, Folder 1873)
      - Purchasing and Shipments: Requisitions (General), 1976 (Box 133, Folder 1874)
      - Purchasing and Shipments: Ongcog, Natividad C. (Officer-in-Charge), 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1875)
      - Purchasing and Shipments: Order Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1876)
      - R - General, 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1877)
      - Reynolds, Hubert, 1976-1979
      - Roble, Maria Conception, 1977-1978 (Box 133, Folder 1878)
      - S - General (Box 133, Folder 1879)
      - School of Communication [see: Maslog, Crispin]
      - Sitoy, T. Valentino [see: Divinity School]
      - Southeast Asian Studies Program [see: Corsino, MacArthur F.]
      - Sycip, Gowes, Velayo Co., C.P.A., 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1879)
      - Sycip, Fe L., 1972-1973 (Box 134, Folder 1880)
      - Tayko, Perla, 1973-1978 (Box 134, Folder 1881)
      - Tiempo, Edilberto K., 1976-1978 (Box 134, Folder 1882)
      - Tiempo, Edith Lopez, 1977-1979 (Box 134, Folder 1883)
      - Trustees - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 134, Folder 1884)
      - Udarbe, Proceso, 1973-1979 (Box 134, Folder 1885-1886)
      - Personal, 1974-1975 (Box 134, Folder 1887)
      - Udarbe, Leonora, 1974-1975 (Box 134, Folder 1888)
      - Van Es, Roland, 1976-1978 (Box 134, Folder 1889)
      - University Research Center [see also: Alcala, Angel C.], 1971-1972 (Box 134, Folder 1890)
      - Van Houweling Laboratory, 1974
      - Yuzon, Lourdino A., 1978
      - Water Pollution Conference, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 1891)
      - Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 1892-1893)
      - Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 1894)
      - Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 1895)
      - Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 1896-1897)
      - Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 1898)
    - Southern Christian College
      - Correspondence - General, 1970-1979 (Box 135, Folder 1899)
      - Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1978-1980 (Box 135, Folder 1900)
    - Trinity College of Quezon City
      - Guerrero, Arturo, 1970-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1901)
      - Informational Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 136, Folder 1902)
      - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1975-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1903)
      - Proposals, Grants, etc., 1977-1980 (Box 136, Folder 1903)
    - Xavier University
      - Correspondence - General, 1974-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1904)
      - Information Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 136, Folder 1905)
      - Institute for the Development of Educational Administrators (I.D.E.A.) Program, 1974-1977 (Box 136, Folder 1906)
      - Overseas Personnel Lists, 1978
      - Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1975-1980 (Box 136, Folder 1907)
  - Taiwan
    - Soochow University
      - Belcher, Morton III, 1972-1978 (Box 136, Folder 1908)
      - Buildings
      - Library, 1973-1975 (Box 136, Folder 1909)
      - Science Hall, 1972-1973 (Box 136, Folder 1910)
      - Student Dormitory, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 1911)
      - Chang, Grace (Librarian), 1972-1974 (Box 136, Folder 1912)
      - Chang, Pei-Yang, 1977-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1913)
      - Denlinger, Paul B., 1976-1979
      - Desbates, Christian, 1973-1976 (Box 136, Folder 1914)
      - Endowment Fund, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 1915)
      - Fellowships, 1972-1976
      - Finance
      - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 136, Folder 1916)
      - Loan Agreements, General, 1972-1977 (Box 136, Folder 1917)
      - Wang, Duncan, 1976-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1918)
      - Fund Raising Workshop, 1973 (Box 136, Folder 1919)
      - Hong, Florence [see: Music Department]
      - Lavery, John, 1970-1977 (Box 136, Folder 1920)
      - Lee, Orlan, 1974-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1921)
      - Lee, Wen-Yi, 1972-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1922)
      - Library, 1976-1978 (Box 137, Folder 1923)
      - Music Department, 1974
      - (incl. Hong, Florence), 1976
      - Overseas Personnel, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 1924)